{
    "title": "CYBR-2500-Final Short Answer",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "At what layer of the OSI model do switches operate?",
            "correct_answer": "Layer 2",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "When a switch attempts to set a port’s operating mode to the highest performance setting, the connecting device that supports it is called?",
            "correct_answer": "Auto-negotiate mode",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "The total number of routers a packet must travel through is called?",
            "correct_answer": "Hop count",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Switches that support ________________________ enable you to configure one or more switch ports into separate broadcast domains.",
            "correct_answer": "Virtual local area networks (VLANs)",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "The process of moving a packet from the incoming interface to the outgoing interface is called?",
            "correct_answer": "Packet Forwarding",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which type of routing protocol shares information with other routers by sending the status of all their interface links to other routers in the internetwork?",
            "correct_answer": "Link-state protocols",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a set of rules configured on a router’s interface for specifying which addresses and which protocols can pass through the interface and to which destinations?",
            "correct_answer": "Access control list",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "In a distance vector routing protocol, where do routers send their routing table information?",
            "correct_answer": "They copy the routing table to other routers on the network.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which AP feature enables you to restrict which devices can connect to your AP based on their physical address?",
            "correct_answer": "MAC filtering",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are credit card–sized expansion cards used mainly to add functionality to laptop computers?",
            "correct_answer": "PCMCIA cards",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which element of a network security policy explains proper or improper use of the Internet?",
            "correct_answer": "Internet Use Policy",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What policy type outlines the policies for backup procedures, virus protection, and disaster recovery?",
            "correct_answer": "Data Protection",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the three levels of security?",
            "correct_answer": "Highly Restrictive, Moderately Restrictive, Open Security",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which policy explains the manner in which security compliance or violations can be verified and what consequences a violation should have?",
            "correct_answer": "Auditing Policy",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the four characteristics of a complex password policy?",
            "correct_answer": "Lowercase letters, Uppercase letters, numbers, and special characters.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What system usually works like a firewall or router with ACLs?",
            "correct_answer": "Intrusion Detection System",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What determines which TCP and UDP ports are available on a particular computer or device?",
            "correct_answer": "Port Scanner",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What device allows you to capture packets and determine which protocols are running?",
            "correct_answer": "Protocol Analyzers",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What attack is an attacker’s attempt to tie up network bandwidth so that it renders resources useless to legitimate users?",
            "correct_answer": "A DoS attack (Denial of Service)",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a program that sends a large number of ping packets to a host?",
            "correct_answer": "A Ping Flood",
            "type": "short_answer"
        }
    ]
}